Seyfarth Shaw Newsclipping File 6350
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Teamsters (IBT), 1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Teamsters (IBT)1979 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1973 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1972 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1971 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Teamsters (IBT), 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Textile Workers (TWUA), 1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Transit (ATU), 2007 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Transit (ATU), 1992-2006 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Transit (ATU), 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Transit (ATU), 1978-1986 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Transit (ATU), 1969-1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Transit (CTA), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Transit (CTA), 1989-2993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Transit CTA, 1983-1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Transit CTA, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Transit CTA, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Dec
- Transit CTA, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Transit CTA, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Transit CTA, 1969-1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Transport Workers (TWU), 1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Transport Workers (TWU), 1970-1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Transportation (UTU), 2000 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Transportation (UTU), 1990-1999 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Transportation (UTU), 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Transportation (UTU), 1978-1985 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Transportation (UTU), 1971-1977 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Transportation (UTU), 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- TV & Radio Artists (AFTRA), 2006 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- TV & Radio Artists (AFTRA), 2000-2005 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Typographers (ITU), 1986 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous "T" (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Unemployment, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Umpires, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Unions - General, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Unions-General, 2000-2005 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Unions-General, 1990-1999 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Unions-General, 1969-1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Unions-Political Activity, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Unions-Political Activity, 1973-1999 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Unions-Political Activity, 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Utility Workers (UWUA), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous U (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Taxi Drivers, 1970-1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Transportation Communications (TCU), 1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Treasury Employees (NTEU), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- TV & Radio Artists (AFTRA), 1969-1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Typographers (ITU), 1978-1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Typographers (ITU), 1969-1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Wage & Price Controls, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Wage & Price Controls, 1972-1976 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Wage & Price Controls, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Wage & Price Controls, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Wage & Price Controls, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  Jul-Aug
- Wire Service Guild, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Writers, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Writers, 1981-1999 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous W (Box 19, Folder 26)
- X-Ray Technicians, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous X Y & Z (Box 19, Folder 28)